(Bernadette:)I know they would-- they did it
to Barbara Chen last year
(Bernadette:)when I told everyone
she was pregnant.
Wait till I Snapchat that
my friends might be working
(Raj:)on a top secret
government project.
(Leonard:)Are you crazy?
(Leonard:)You can't put that on Snapchat.
(Raj:)Fine, I'll put it on Facebook
like a caveman.
(Penny:)You know,
maybe before our meeting
(Howard:)we should talk to a lawyer.
(Leonard:)That's not a bad idea.
(Raj:)Well, you must have someone
in your family that's a lawyer.
(Howard:)Why? Because I'm Jewish?
(Howard:)That's like me saying,
"Hey, you're Indian.
(Howard:)Doesn't your cousin work
in a call center?"
(Raj:)My cousin does work
in a call center.
(Howard:)And my cousin's a lawyer.
- We don't need Howard's cousin.
- No?
(Sheldon:)We have me.
(Leonard:)You're not a lawyer, Sheldon,
you're just a know-it-all.
(Sheldon:)I am not a know-it-all.
(Sheldon:)I'm a person
who knows lots of things
(Sheldon:)and likes to correct
other people when they're wrong.